I'll start the recording though,
just so I can start us off then.
We wanted to do 2 things today,
so I'll be set 2 minutes.
Number one,
I think they're during quarterly planning.
We were talking about how you guys have
done some work already or maybe you've
completed some work for the Bright SDK
for talent pools.
And then we are also doing some work for
the Bright control panel.
I think they're now calling it the Bright
admin console for like all agents or all
AI things.
So we were doing some work on that for
Job Genius,
since that's what's live and out there
for recruiting right now and moving Job
Genius into that Bright control panel,
which is just a,
a fancy way of saying they're going to be
able to turn all AI things from that
bright control panel.
So since Job Genius is the one real AI
thing that we have out there in
recruiting,
then that's where we're moving it to.
And then I think the expectation is,
is for all of these other agents,
these new ones that we're bringing to the
market to have those also be able to get
enabled in that bright control panel.
So just sharing the work that we did for
Job Genius as well.
So it sounds like everybody else is going
to have to be doing those things soon for
their own agents that they're bringing to
the market.
So that's kind of the scope of this call.
It's probably going to be more than 30
minutes if any of us have like a ton of
questions about the work.
But I think for the Bright Control panel,
it's a couple of stories that we worked
on.
I think what is like with a lot of things,
the difficulties come when you're trying
to test these things because I think even
for us,
for the bright control panel for Job
Genius,
it wasn't tested in our normal like suite
end to end environment that we know of.
It was in a different environment.
So just keeping those things in mind.
Hey, Abby.
Hello.
I'm sorry for being late.
Yeah, I completely missed that,
that we have a meeting right now.
Thanks, Josh for no worries.
So I gave them the rundown.
Today's meeting is basically we want to
talk about the Bright control panel since
we are doing that work for Job Genius and
then for Deep D's team,
they want to understand that because I
think it it applies to interview
Scorecard.
And then we also would like to ask them
about the Bright SDK since it sounds like
they did some work for talent pools.
So we're just kind of sharing some
details about all of those things.
So that's about the,
the scope of this call.
It may be more than 30 minutes, we'll see.
It just kind of depends on how many
questions we have.
So do we want to start with Bright
Control Panel or Bright SDK?
If,
if you can give us like if you can show
us like how Bright control panel will
look like,
like just if you have any Sigma around it
or maybe how it will appear in our
application.
If you can give a walkthrough about that,
that will be great.
Yeah.
And I see you don't really need a Figma.
We will give you the real product.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anything will work.
Yeah.
OK.
So let me quickly show you then that
first we will start with BCP,
then give me one second.
My machine is not,
I was not prepared and in the meantime
I'll be,
I like to you know mention which was
discussed in last call since Diego was
there with Jen Baker.
We since BCP is still in their beta,
they are not going to Georgia with R1.
So having our agents into BCP is not a
mandate for Georgia as of now until BCP
goes for Georgia itself.
So we are safe on that part.
I mean Nasib,
if you won't be able to pick up right now
for this work that that's OK.
We can plan it, but we can have the,
you know,
overview like how that thing needs to be
done.
OK, All right.
This is being recorded already.
And can you guys see my screen?
Yes, awesome.
And thank you Deepti for that
clarification that it's not needed yet.
So that was helpful.
Yeah.
And on that note of the sorry Avi of it
not being needed, I'm,
I'm trying to meet with Ankur because I
was curious where if the bright control,
if we're not using bright control panel,
if someone in let's say that, you know,
can't sourcing or interview scorecard
someone like buys that in like the bright
skew.
Like how would we know as recruiting that
we need to activate that launch darkly
toggle?
You know what I mean?
Like,
how would we know to enable the feature?
I, I don't know.
So I,
I think I'm reaching out to someone from
the right team to ask them what are we
supposed to do there?
Does that make sense?
If it is so if it is not in BCP,
then how do we enable that is your
question right?
Yeah, like, right,
because all these are behind launch
darkly.
So that makes sense for me.
But how would how would we know when to
enable?
Like is someone emailing us?
Do we need to, do they have to call some?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, that's an open question.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm asking them like,
what are we supposed to do?
Like for now, is it just, hey,
you'll you'll let us know?
I mean, that's probably OK.
But yeah,
that's the only part that I'm confused on.
It's how would we notify it?
So I'm gonna, I'll look into that.
OK.
Awesome.
Thank you.
OK,
so this is one of the in the suite
environment there is a separate tenant.
So as recruiting team,
we all use a specific tenant.
It starts with ARNI don't know the full
name of the tenant,
but that is the one that we use for suite
end to end testing.
All of us, this is a separate tenant.
It is not that fun.
And in this one you have UKG auth and
enabled and you have recruiting enabled
and Pro is enabled.
And in this one,
you have the full BCP functionality.
The other one,
the one that we regularly use,
cannot have,
cannot have BCP because of some issues
with authen.
Unless and until Authen is not available,
then BCP cannot be available on on that
tenant.
So let's navigate to Bright Control Panel
and you can hear application setup,
system configuration,
and then we go to Bright Admin Console.
So this is your Bright Control panel.
As you can see here also Bright Control.
And here we have Job Genius.
This is the one for which we have done
the implementation part.
So Administrator is going to come to this
page.
They turn on Bright AI and then they turn
on Job Genius, for example,
every 12 hours.
We have written heartbeat code on the
recruiting side,
which hits their API and checks whether
this thing,
this feature is enabled or not.
Yes, Diego, do we ever?
What were the takeaways from that Slack
chat with the Bright team?
Did they say that we just live with the
calling each tenant one at a time every
12 hours?
Yes, right now we are there only there is,
we are,
we are calling each tenant every 12 hours.
There is a bulk end point,
but our team has not implemented that.
I am not sure where is that?
I said Alex Sabatino,
is that the name right?
Yeah, Alex from our team.
Yeah.
Alex from your team.
Yes, exactly.
So he is the one who probably is,
you know, gonna use the new endpoint.
That's what he said in the chat as did we
create that endpoint already or or did
they?
I I don't remember what was the final say
from the bright team?
Because I remember we needed them to do
something.
So they had they had one endpoint,
but they had called it that do not use
for production.
But then over the chat they said that you
can you can use it for production for now.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
So they do have the endpoint,
but they initially said that that is not
supposed to be used.
OK, All right, so coming back to here.
So administrator comes here and they turn
on Job Genius every 12 hours.
We have implemented a heartbeat on our
side and that heartbeat checks the status
of of this flag if it is on or off.
And based on that,
we turn on or off our feature here for
Job Genius.
Right now it is on and the heartbeat must
is currently running at everyday Eastern
Time.
I don't know with the daylight,
the time changed from the 7:00 or 8:00 PM
yeah, either.
So it was running at 7:00 PM or and 7:00
AM earlier.
Now it is either 8 or 6,
I don't know whichever way.
And here you can see that you can see
Bright AI here.
Use Bright AI for job description.
Use Bright AI for interview questions for
these settings.
These settings are enabled.
And if you try to go and create an
opportunity,
you can see here Draft with bright AI,
Draft with Bright AI,
all these buttons are enabled.
And same thing for interview questions
too.
It's in the screening tab,
interview questions here,
drafted bright AI.
So all these features are enabled.
And if somebody turns it off right now,
then whenever the heartbeat runs,
let's say whatever it's like today at
7:00 PM, it runs,
then it will go ahead and turn off all
these features at 7:00 PM.
Yes, Diego,
when you click the switch in the bright
control panel,
is it turning on the setting or just
surfacing the setting?
I am not clicking on it yet.
I just searched it here.
That's all I did so far during this
meeting.
Right, right, right.
I'm, I'm just saying,
let's say it was turned off, right?
Yeah.
Does it hide all the does it hide the
bright AI settings in in recruiting?
Yes, it will,
it will it will hide this guy also this
in the settings.
It this this will not be visible anymore.
OK.
And then when you turn it back on in
bright control panel,
does it just surface the settings or does
it also surface plus turn on the setting?
Does that make sense?
Surface plus turn on, yes.
Gotcha.
But it but it will happen at that time
that whenever the heartbeat runs, right,
it is not instantaneous.
Yeah.
Because the way that I thought we would
do it is probably just surface it and
then still let the admin turn it on or
let the recruiter person turn it on.
But I know we we were still talking about
it.
OK, At least for for canned sourcing.
That's what that,
that was my initial thoughts on it.
So, OK, yeah,
whichever way we decide to implement that,
yes, yeah, I was just curious.
Yeah, awesome.
Yeah,
that's a good question to keep in mind
because if there are other things that
you require to turn on your agent,
like I know for Job Genius,
there's like 2 fields you have to fill
out when you're in that bright AI
settings for that.
So we're not surfacing any of that here,
right?
When you turn it on.
Also,
I don't know if you want to turn it on
and show them that message where it says
like it'll be on in the next 30 minutes.
Did we see that message?
I don't think because we should turn this
on, right and this right.
Yeah.
Whenever you whenever you toggle it,
it shows that 30 minute message,
which is misleading in my opinion.
It should say up to 12 hours.
It was 30 Hispanic minutes.
That's what I would say, yes, basically.
OK, Deepti, like did I,
did we answer your question like I or did
you have a question on that or you're
just pointing it out?
Oh, me, I was just pointing it out.
I didn't know if anybody else had seen
this before.
So I was just pointing out all the things
that we know about it so far.
So that 30 minute message thing was
another thing that it's funny because it
doesn't turn on in the next 30 minutes
for us.
So you have to wait until the heartbeat.
So, yeah, OK, sorry.
Go ahead, Deepti.
So I mean,
you have already answered my first
question what Diego has asked.
So that was my first one.
So second Abhi.
So in this case,
now if I understood it correct,
it is like once the setting on this
bright admin console first,
if it's enabled and the settings on our
recruiting bright AI is enabled,
then only I'm able to see my feature.
I mean whatever feature we have a bright
enable feature.
Let's suppose consider a case the setting
over here of I mean this on the bright
admin console this toggle is turned on.
But on recruiting side,
someone has turned off the right AI
toggle.
This when you say turned off the toggle
like toggle means through the Mongo DB,
right?
Both ways, let's say through Mongo DB.
OK,
let's first consider through Mongo DB
then in that case anyways, I mean,
we are not going to access the features,
bright enabled features, right?
No.
So when the heartbeat runs,
it will check OK, it is on here.
So it will turn on the toggles that Mongo
DB toggles on our side.
It will turn on the toggle automatically,
yes.
What if a customer has decided that for a
momentary or for some time,
they don't want to, you know,
turn on the bright toggle,
so they turn it off here.
This should be the final source of truth.
Yeah.
So if that is ultimately probably, yeah,
we might want to remove it here from here
completely.
Yeah.
That, that that is what I'm right.
This is what I'm coming to.
Like then we do not require the settings
of on our side.
This would be the source for all the
control on on the bright features, right?
Exactly.
So that is the whole point of this bright
control panel.
All the bright related features will be
controlled here through the whole UKG
like not just recruiting for everything.
As you can see here, all the agents,
everything will be controlled here.
OK, gotcha, Gotcha.
Yeah, thank you.
No problem, Naseeb.
Yeah, I just want to know,
like I can see there are 63 total
settings here, right?
Out of which 55 are active, right?
OK, So yeah,
this page is not specific to us, right?
Like right, maybe it is pro specific,
right?
And what are the settings that we need to
do?
And now going ahead,
if you want to add interview scorecard
agent settings here,
then we'll add one more option, right,
Right.
And instead of turning on the bright,
the launch darkly toggle,
we will turn on the toggle here on and
off.
And according to that,
it will be visible on our recruiting side.
This should be the end goal or like,
right, Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right.
Now what we want to do is so keep your
launch darkly toggle and when you turn it
on here like suppose you add the add your
interview scorecard here then you will
put that code in the heartbeat that every
12 hours it is gonna check whether it is
on or not interview scorecard is on or
not here.
If it is on then turn on the launch
startly toggle on on the recruiting side.
If it is off here then turn off the
launch startly toggle on your side behind
the scenes.
OK, one more related question,
like which which team is responsible for
adding just for like for my learning
purpose,
which team is responsible for adding an
option here?
Like do we need to do our own or like
there is a different team on pro site
that add this option the way we are
responsible the MX, right?
Yeah, it's, it's our responsibility.
So they have created documentation for
that on how to how to add a feature.
And currently we are following that
documentation also to add a new feature.
When I started working on this job genius
one job genius one already existed.
So I did not have to go through this pain,
but right now I'm working on another
feature for our rec candidate assist on
the job board, the Ava chat feature.
So for that one,
I'm I'm trying to add that and I'm
basically there is a there is a couple of
steps that you need to follow.
There is a specific repo to which you
need to create your PR against against
that repo and get that get approvals for
for that specific your agent.
And once it goes through that,
then it will start showing up as a
capability.
They call it capability behind theirs
behind the scenes in the APIs.
So you will have to add the capability.
OK, Yeah.
So I can share that documentation
separately on how to how to add your
capability to Bright control panel.
OK, Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
And Ankur, Ankur Arora is,
is from their team and Manjul Dikshit,
these are the two people,
two key people whom you will have to get
approvals from whenever you have the PR
ready.
OK, Are we all good?
Cool.
I think now we could switch over to the
SDK.
Yeah.
OK, so before I start like Abhi,
like I shared few documents with you like
did did you get any chance to go through
that like or I can start from my
introduction?
I think you will have to start from
scratch.
I tried to look at it but did not get a
chance to dig deeper into it.
OK, let me share my screen.
Let me know if it is visible.
Then maybe I'll just walk through what we
have achieved so far and what will be the
end goal.
Let me know if my screen is visible.
Is it visible?
Yeah.
OK, let me go to the dashboard page.
Right.
This is our recruiting app and this is
our rec preview environment.
I'm navigating to the pools page.
So this is the pool page which we created
for our talent pool work.
And this is not an existing pool page.
We have a manual way of creating a pool,
right?
But like this is only creating through a
bright.
So we have created altogether a different
page which will serve only that will
create a pool through bright, right?
So only one option will be visible either
this pool which is stating the bright
talent pool or maybe there is another
pool which will simply say the pool page
something like this, right?
Just just for the understanding that you
are landing to the correct page or not.
If I toggle is on,
we will be navigating to bright with
talent pool page.
If our toggle is off,
we will be landing to the old pool page
that comes with the new navigation,
not the one which is which has the legacy
one right?
And if you see on the like the bottom
right corner,
we have it this bright assist MFE micro
content right?
If I click it here,
the bright assist window will open and it
comes with a welcome message.
Hi, I am Bright.
What can I do for you today?
And here what you need to do is simply
tell the agent that what you want to
perform.
Like if I say if I'm on a talent pool
page,
if I simply type create a talent pool,
right?
So this is my first instruction and it
will search for the agents that we have
registered on to the Bright Hub and it
will find the subsequent result.
If, if, if it is present,
if you can see the instructions as well.
This instruction is coming up.
I'm pulling up the right tool for your
request.
So now this request has been successfully
interacted with our agent.
That is why we are seeing this response.
Yeah, go ahead Abhi.
So you are showing the product demo here.
I thought we were just gonna look at the
SDK or is that something for everyone
that other people are also interested in
looking at the product demo?
It is up to you.
Like if you want to go into the technical
and see the implementation.
This is just a walk through for one.
One.
Yeah, OK.
Yeah, for me,
I wanted to look at the technical stuff
only, but if, if,
since I know product is also here.
So that's why I am raising that question.
Like what's the purpose of so I'll,
I'll not like take too much time onto
this, right?
OK, So this is simple,
simple the instructions, right?
So our agent has been invoked like we
have trained our agents.
If we get the responses in this form as
the next question here,
I'm saying that I am looking for creating
a talent pool for product managers with
the experience of this range 5 to 20
years.
Right now,
there are some set of suggestions that is
given by the agent what skills you are
looking for.
You can type your or you can type
whatever you receive from the AI, right?
And we are building,
we are building the pool on the basis of
four criteria as of now.
We'll be further extended other criterias
as well.
But as of now, there are 4 criterias.
1 is the skill,
another is a number of years of
experience,
3rd is the employer type and 4th 1 is the
region.
Right.
So we haven't created anything for this
UI.
It is directly achieved through the
Bright SDK.
And if I say yes this is the criteria and
it looks good to me,
I can simply say confirm and proceed.
It has found 33 candidate based on the
criteria that I have entered and and now
this pool is live.
If I refresh or maybe check in a while
then we can see one more one pool created
on our pool page just still loading.
Let me yeah,
this is has been created with a number of
candidate as this is just a walkthrough
right as of now.
Like there are not so many teams who have
adopted the Bright SDK which are outside
of Pro.
So we have this provision not to use the
bright assist as well.
We can simply do it the way we did for
the interview scorecard.
We simply create like we can simply
create a pool through Bright through this
button as well.
And this is the UI which we created it
and the experience will be same in both
the cases.
So this is the additional thing that we
did for the talent pool as of now.
Maybe going forward we can remove this
button functionality and only creating a
pool through the bright assist now.
Now coming to the technical part,
basically they have provided a CDN that
will help us to load the micro front end
at our end.
If if you see this confluence with that
is why I asked.
I checked with you that did you get
chance to go through the documentation.
It is pretty much straightforward.
This is the CDN that they have provided
it.
You have to use this CDN on your STML or
maybe your CSTML page right?
If you want to render this MFV icon,
this MFV icon,
you need to simply use this element UKG
bright shell, bright assist shell,
give the IDs of it,
give the headers of it.
These are the launch darkly fields that
are optional if you want to give it right
similarly local and this is the search
dispatch URL.
So,
so as of now what we are doing is we are
creating our agents into the NREC repo,
right?
We have a different repo, right.
But if you want to use Bright SDK your
your agent should lie into the Suitex
search because now we are consume going
through the Bright SDK approach and they
are using Suitex URL to identify or fetch
the agent right?
Like I mentioned create talent pool.
If your pool is lie under the NREC it
will not able to find it because now we
are going through the suitex search and
like this is the only way to achieve it.
So my agent that that I'm interacting in
this bright assist is lie under the
suitex search not the NREC.
I can by this means I'm saying that we,
our agent should lie under the Suitex
search, not the NREC, right.
So this is the pre request if you want to
adopt the brightest decay.
So alright Josh, where is ours?
Is it under NREC or is it under Suitex?
I thought it was under Suitex.
No, it's under, it's under NREC.
Yeah.
Oh OK.
So there is no issue in doing it.
We can simply copy paste like earlier.
We are also thinking that we can consume
through NREC but once we get the clarity
that we have to move our agent through
Suitex,
we can simply copy paste the Jason and
create a raise a PR to move into the
Suitex.
OK right.
So all you need to use this HTML tag,
this element UKG bright shell right?
If if your request is supposed to receive
any token as well,
you can send it through in a header using
your token, right?
Instead of using the X custom header,
you need to set the accept context.
I'll I'll come come to that later, right.
So there are two URLs that we need to
find it as as per their documentation,
we need to find that URL through DX,
right?
So if you see it here the instruction one
is we need to fetch the CDN, right?
CDN that we are using it here,
line number, this thing right?
This is a CDN that we need to fetch it
right?
We cannot use in a hard coded way.
We cannot simply give this URL right.
What we need to do is we need to navigate
we need to fetch this URL through TRX
using the service code.
This is the service code that I'm using
to fetch this URL SX SX SDK CDN and there
is another URL such dispatch URL which
also need to fetch from the T Rex.
So similarly for that as well that like.
So if we just Simply put it in the
JavaScript it will not work like this.
It will work like this but it is not
suggested.
See if you see it here as well.
They are stating it to dev right.
Similarly in this search URL it is also
stating dev right for upper environment.
You need to go through the T Rex only
right I So if you want.
So the way you have implemented it is
like you fetch the URL from whatever
service like your config file or whatever
and then you plug it in here in this
JavaScript, yes.
So these changes are already in the rec
preview.
So what we did is we simply gave the
service code and that data center
environment type,
we'll get this static URL.
Static URL is static asset URL is no
longer reading now needed now.
Earlier it was required,
but it is no longer needed.
Needed now.
SDK URL, the CDN one and the gateway URL,
these are the two URLs that you need to
fetch through the TRS.
OK, right.
And once you do that,
it will work for you, right?
There are some additional properties that
you can play around that are still near
to me.
Yeah.
So we have to plug in this JavaScript.
We have to follow the code part that you
have that you just showed of fetching the
URLs.
What about the interaction?
Interaction with the agent?
Because right now the way we have
implemented our agent is we are doing raw
API calls for for the agent.
We send out the message and then we get
the response back.
And every time we get the response back,
we display it on the UI.
But these are all raw API calls.
So I think my understanding was that this
SDK will create a wrapper around those
raw API.
Yeah, you don't need to.
You don't need to do anything explicitly
for that.
You don't need to create a session for it.
Sutex will create a session for it.
It will give you the response.
It will like you can make a request.
If you see this,
let me show you something maybe.
Oh,
so you are not relaying the message from
your application anymore?
No, we are going via the proxy.
OK, we are going via the proxy.
If you see it here,
let the response come right.
So all you need to do is traverse this
event stream and it will display
automatically in this bright assist
window, right?
I'm not creating any session for it.
I'm not doing anything specifically that
we did for the interview scorecard of
sending the criteria from here, right?
All I need to do is just to render this
UI and invoke an agent.
Agent response will be rendered
automatically in this Bright assist
window.
If you want to specifically decorate your
responses,
you can do that output configuration onto
the Bright hub side.
There is documentation for that as well.
I can share it with you or maybe you can
see in the related conference that I
shared it with you earlier.
Now coming back so so now this is this is
the confluence of the back end
implementation, right?
Like I said,
if if our request requires some
authentication or authorization,
you need to send that authorization token
in a header.
Whereas there is only one difference.
Like I said,
we cannot use X custom header attribute
in a header.
We have to use accept context header as
we are outside of pro.
So this is the specific header that we
need to use.
So if you see in accept context there are
few required fields that you need to pass.
One is the tenant ID, user ID,
service code, deployment identifier.
So what it did is whatever you specify it
here,
sue text will eventually invoke your
endpoint.
Maybe I can show you through code as well.
This is the talent pool right?
I'm I'm setting up this accept context in
my HTML page where like I said you need
to specify the service code TRS service
code.
So our rec service code is H rec our API
you need to give the deployment
identifier right?
If it is dev or GCP or US E 1.
Similarly the environment type and this
is a user context part.
This is the endpoint that you need to
provide it right?
So eventually sue text will land up to
this endpoint.
And if this endpoint requires any source
of authentication or authorization,
you need to pass in a header right?
And once it lands to this endpoint,
it will actually authenticate either you
are a valid product,
it it should give a result of a user or
maybe a tenant that it is a valid user
and it is valid talent tenant and it is a
valid product, right?
If I show you the implementation of this
as well, OK, session details.
So this is basically so Sutex will call
our this endpoint, right?
We will check either the tenant we have
received is valid, OK, right.
OK.
So once it's more of what's the word for
it?
Like basically you put in the endpoints
and then they will call these endpoints
like you still have to,
you will have to implement these
endpoints, right, right.
This is for the for the first interaction.
Once that interaction is successful,
you can simply make a connection and
interact with your agent.
This is for first connection.
OK,
first like once you are initializing the
bright assist on your side,
they need to authenticate you that you
are a valid product,
you are a valid user or a valid tenant.
OK, right, right.
But just to add on,
see bright assist is not only like given
to use on a specific page.
Ideally it should be available throughout
the application, not on the pool page.
As of now,
our requirement is to have it on a pool
page.
Ideally it should be on the maybe a
dashboard on every page, right?
And we can perform whatever actions we
want to do it.
This is the end goal.
So Bright SDKS implemented as of now.
What I did is I placed this MFE onto my
page.
You don't need to adopt the Bright SDK
because it is already done.
If I move this icon onto the dashboard or
the layout page,
it will be available to you as well right?
OK, yes,
so you so you don't need to adopt Bright
SDK again, got it.
OK, OK, right.
OK.
If you,
because the purpose of Bright assist is
to provide a kind of a chat window or a
help window throughout your pages on
every pages, right?
If you see on a pro as well,
we have this bright MFV icon on every
page or maybe on the landing page, right?
And you can simply interact through it.
Let navigate me to the locations,
navigate me to the user roles, right?
You can do it each and every operations,
whatever you want to perform.
So this has been adopted but as of now I
have placed it onto the talent pool page.
Eventually it should go out and if I say
it here create a talent pool,
it should create a talent pool.
If I say create an interview scorecard,
it will invoke the instructions for the
interview scorecard right through this
page as well whatever page you want.
But right now it does not right?
Like even if there is multiple then
multiple multiple AI agents associated
with recruiting application,
I don't think we have the IT will know
how to route to which agent.
So,
so to route to which agent that you need
to train through the bright hub only,
right?
If I show you here, let me refresh it,
right.
So this is our agent.
If you see it examples here, right?
You need to write few examples,
create a pool, generate a talent pool,
create a talent community,
create a candidate pool.
So whenever we type anything specific to
this in our bright assist,
it will find automatically, OK, right.
And that is the additional step that you
need to do.
And in Bright Assist,
you cannot configure the first welcome
message.
It will always show you, hi,
what can I do for you, right?
If I say create a interview scorecard
right now, what will happen?
There is no such instruction or no such
intent.
Training has been set up for this thing.
It will result into nothing.
Let's see if you see it here right?
Nothing happened specific to the
interview scorecard.
It will only perform whatever the
instructions that you.
So whenever you are creating an agent,
even you can modify your existing agent
and add these instructions.
Once you add these instructions,
the Bright SDK will invoke your agent.
Right.
OK,
so now the way I'm thinking is that I
don't yeah, it looks like multi agent.
I don't know how this would work for
consent.
That is also true.
There has to be a common consent across
recruiting then.
That's a very good point, Josh.
Yeah.
What am I?
I was gonna ask,
I was gonna ask is this needed?
Because this is a lot of work to read,
like to redo our agent to be compatible
with this.
Yeah.
So moving the agent to the other part
then?
Yeah,
like this is only putting in the
JavaScript, then making the hook, yeah,
the web hook again that that Nasib showed
for session creation and all that stuff.
And then cleaning up all the code for
relaying the messages that we have right
now.
And then and then that's why I'm thinking
I'm like, well,
how will how will we do consent then?
Like our curb implementation of consent
because we show like a custom message
right before, but this looks like,
like it's just all controlled by the
agent side with instructions.
Yeah, as of now,
we cannot modify the first message.
Yes, exactly.
So it's like,
and that's feedback that I can give back
to the Bright SDK team, right?
Because that was one of my questions that
I had for Naseeb is when you were
implementing this,
did you run into anything that let's say
you needed for pools,
but the Bright SDK doesn't allow you to
do that.
Like our consent is a good example of
that.
And another good example is there is no
like upload option that you really can
get with the bright SDK right?
Like that bright assist MFE that you were
showing.
There's nowhere to like upload a resume
because I know for our chat bot on the
job board, right?
For it to be very useful for a candidate,
they'd wanna be able or we'd wanna be
able to allow them to upload a resume,
right?
Maybe you have some skills in your resume
that we could import and use to identify
and match you to a job.
So we did let the SDK team know about
that cuz there's not really I think an
option for that right now.
And they are aware,
I'm not sure about that uploading thing,
but there can be provision,
but I need to check like because that is
not our requirement so far.
So we haven't focused on to that as of
now.
Right, right, right.
So that's what I'm saying.
Outside of that,
did you run into anything that you were
looking to implement?
It just it wasn't available from their
side.
So one thing that is that I already
mentioned that we cannot tweak the
welcome message, right?
Another recommendation is that that
earlier our requirement is to when I hit
onto this button create pool with bright,
it should open a assist window,
not this window the this window, right?
So for that as well we need to do some
tweaks.
We can achieve that,
but their recommendation is to not to do
by this way.
If you want to open a bright assist,
simply create MFE.
Also,
there are some configurations like
suppose if I want to decorate my response
in a form of chips or maybe in form of
some another markup, right?
That is also limited like in a In this
case, if we are receiving some response,
what we what we do is we simply decorate
in a form of chips, right?
But in a case of bright assist,
if the response is coming from the if the
response is coming from your REST tool,
this is a little bit maybe I can explain
you what is the REST tool, Abhi,
you must be aware it aware about it.
So these are the REST tools for the APIs
that we have set up.
Suppose yes,
I am entering some criteria and now like
I said,
UX designer number of years is this
employee type is internal location is
California, right?
Eventually it will fetch the results and
how it will fetch the result it will call
our API and for that we need to configure
this REST tool right?
If the output is coming from the REST
tool, we can decorate it in any form,
maybe in chips, table, buttons.
But if your output is given by the AI,
suppose I said that UX designer, right?
The next question is asked for to me is
what skills you are looking for?
There are 10 skills which is given by the
AI.
That is not given by our API.
That is given by the AI.
For that there is a scope.
There is a limitation where we cannot
decorate it in a form of chips.
This is another challenge which I face.
If you want I can reiterate it right?
If I say create a talent pool, right.
So first thing is I'm get getting this
text right.
What role you are looking for?
If I say UX designer,
let's see if the response come.
Now,
if I want to show these things in a form
of chip, I cannot do that.
As of now.
There is a limitation.
With the bright assist,
we can simply use the text, right?
See these are the these are the skills
given by the AI, not from our API,
not from our endpoint.
If I want to decorate it in a form of
chips,
by chips means the action button like if
I simply click it, it will select.
So I cannot decorate it in that form.
This is another limitation that I feel
that I feel on the brightest side,
whereas the similar we can control it on
our end.
So can you show me that on your side?
Yeah.
Let me quickly jump to the scorecard
template.
The thing is, Vicky,
the way that we have been set set up
right now and even with our screenshots,
we wouldn't be able to do any of it for
this.
Can you see this?
Yeah.
So these are the chips.
We can simply select it right And capture
our response.
So skills right.
Interesting.
Did you provide this feedback to them?
Did they have anything to to mention
about Oh,
maybe we could work on including this
these as chips instead of just like as a
listlet that that we just saw.
So,
so they have a work around for this like
if,
if your chips are hard coded like every
time,
if you get the user research wireframing
and prototyping, right,
if this is the result every time you can
decorate in a form of chips.
But that like that is not our case
because that is responses are coming from
the AI.
It can be vary at different time, right,
right, right, right, right.
Because I'm looking at that like for our
job, Abby and Josh,
when you get the list of jobs right,
they're like links that you can click on.
I don't know how bright assist or yeah,
SDK would handle that.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, we would have to it, it would,
I think allow us because that comes from
the tool.
A response comes from the tool.
So he's saying like anything from a tool,
you can, you can format any type of UI.
OK,
But the consent though is still we don't
it doesn't the consent we cannot do at
all.
Because yeah,
if you think about the the chat,
the chat is is bright like front end,
like they own the code for that.
And like we can't tell it to display a
it's like right here.
It says high on bright and that's the
first message always.
So we can't even even,
they would type and then then we would
have to call, call an API, which we just,
we just cancelled that story,
which was to get the consent message.
We would call an API to grab that message
so it can be formatted how we want before
letting them continue like that would be
the only way.
But yeah, this is, it'll be,
it's like redoing our whole thing,
what we have right now.
Yeah, if it's really needed, I mean,
it probably can be done,
but it definitely not like by April or or
anything.
No, this is,
this is not gonna be for us to do by beta
for sure.
Cuz that's what that's what we're trying
to work on now.
It's just let's get us to beta.
And the SDK is not going to be done for
that, but for Georgia, right,
the general availability part of this
where it goes live to everyone,
I have a feeling that they're going to
want us to be on SDKI know that Didi
already mentioned like for R1,
things that are going GASDK is not
required,
but we're not going GA in R1 or May or
whatever that is, right?
We're going beta.
So the GA discussion for bright SDK is
still going to be ongoing.
But things like this, like our consent,
I can definitely bring up to that team
and say,
how are you guys solving for this?
Because Bright right now is really set up
for like if you are an employee,
it's not really set up or if you are an
external candidate that has nothing to do
with being an employee at the company yet,
right?
So it's not they don't really care about
consent because you're already an
employee, right?
So I think that's that's where the the
difference lies.
So, but yeah,
this is definitely something I can bring
back to that the SDK team and say,
what do you guys have for this?
Because if you guys haven't solved for
this yet,
then I can't really say in good
conscience that we're gonna be able to
move to SDK for even Georgia, right?
So it's a good conversation to have.
So like so as you can, yeah,
you can configure this output through
this, right.
The output that we are getting from the
tool, the REST tool,
we can configure it and in any form.
But output that is generating to the
bright that cannot be configured.
You can use table here you can use
markdown,
you can use markdown string template,
action buttons, whatever you can do.
Yeah,
go ahead to be you are asking something
now.
I was saying that.
So, OK, so the SDK is available to us.
It is there added as a project.
It's just that we have to do the UI work
and set these sessions and move it,
move the agent to to the bright like to
the Suite X, right.
This is the main things to do for our
from our side.
And other than that, yeah,
the challenges that we are just
discussing.
So our first step would be that move a
copy of your agent into the Sultex, right,
right.
And don't move,
don't move it like make a copy of it into
Sultex and try to invoke, right.
And in your instructions,
you are specifying some markdown, right?
We are specifying some markdown,
markdown to display the responses like
this or that if if the Jasons come in the
response render this in render in this
form.
Are you doing Oh yes, something like that,
yes, right, yes.
So now you are doing through assist,
you need to modify your instructions as
well, right.
Oh, another thing OK,
is you need to register your Brite to
register with Brite.
I think you haven't done it for your
agent because it is not requirement if we
are doing in a raw way right?
And there is Ald toggle to get your agent
available.
So one is the register with bright,
another is 1 raises GR request which will
be a feature flag request pose that only
your agent will be available.
Another thing is you you need to do is
the intent classifier means how you will
identify your agent will be invoked.
For that you need to do this intent
classifier.
If you see it here,
my agent is lying it here,
so you need to do it.
I I can share the technical process or
how to raise a PR for it,
I'll share it with you.
And once you do that,
suppose that only your agent will be
available through the bright assist.
OK, no.
So I remember Vicky Ankur was asking me
for adding it to the BCP also like for
adding it adding this Ava our our agent
to BCP,
he was asking me have you registered it
through Bright or not and all that stuff.
And now I understand if we do not go
through this step,
then we can't even effectively or we
would have to change the approach on how
to add it to BCP.
Also because Ankur is expecting that our
agent is right now registered there in
Bright,
which is not right because if we go put
it in Suite X and then only it will be
available.
So these two steps are integrated with
each other or we will have to ask Ankur
to give us an exception on Ava that this
is not something that is registered
through Brite.
This is a separate thing like a job
genius.
Job genius is as as it is completely
separate.
So interview scorecard as well is not
registered with right.
Also intent classification is not done
for the interview scorecard as well
because that is not required if we are
interacting directly with our agent.
And this intent classification is
something that is,
that is allow us to find our agent, right?
That is at the recruiting level,
like not just at one page level, right?
So that is specific to the agent level.
No, no,
that is specific to the agent level.
If you want to invoke specific agent,
right, for each agent, you need to do it.
If you see it here and there is a
challenge understood.
But what that will do is effectively is
that if you call,
if you ask for job recommendations, our,
our API,
our AI provides job recommendations.
So if you ask it even on the talent pool
then also it will respond like no no you
need to add intent classifier for your
agent.
This is the global tenant ID right?
If if it should be available for each
tenant,
it should be null like empty good right
and agent and the agent name.
Then only it will find your agent through
bright assist.
So there are two things.
One is you need to add the examples like
I showed it to you examples here, right,
that if you receive anything specific to
this right.
Another thing is to you need to do the
intent classification.
See this is a golden phrases testing.
If I select it here, right?
Let me try agent, right,
So here what you do do is add your
phrases, right?
So this will be added.
So whenever you type something similar to
this through assist,
it will eventually invoke your agent.
This is basically a training that you are
giving right, right, right.
Now by by by by doing this,
if I say create a talent pool on any page
inside recruiting,
it will it will trigger Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
That's eventually it should be like this
only, right?
It should not specific because the MFE
purpose is it should be available on each
and every page, not on a specific page,
right?
That's what I'm trying to say.
So OK, so this will make it available.
It is it will make it like whole
recruiting in any recruiting and
application within recruiting application.
If you call this, oh,
I'm looking for search for job or I'm
looking to create a pool,
it will trigger it irrespective of the
page on which right, right, right, right.
If I simply move this MFE to some another
page and I simply write this instruction,
it will work for me.
Got it.
So it it knows like what agent,
it'll just use another agent that we have
that with those intents.
Like right now it's using a talent pool
agent.
But if I said I need a job, for example,
and and that is connect like that intent
is through Ava's agent,
it'll know to just go to Ava's agent.
Yeah, in our in our agent, in our agent,
we will mention that our intent is job
recommendation, right.
So once we mentioned that, then anytime,
anywhere it sees that OK,
I'm looking for a job,
then our agent will get triggered and it
will ask for job recommendations from our
side.
But yeah,
the consent part is still up in the air.
In that case.
It also might be weird if it's on the on
like talent blue page for example.
And then you say find me a job.
Well, actually,
actually I guess that's the candidate's
side.
So maybe maybe it won't do that.
I was just trying to think of like it'll
then prompt consent,
which is kind of weird because it just
let you do a bunch of things or yeah,
there is lots of education internal.
Even if you're an internal candidate,
don't you have to agree to that first
consent that you have in?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you would right as well,
even if that, that's what they,
even if you're an internal candidate yeah
like if you wanted to find internal jobs
here,
like it just did a bunch of stuff and
then it's gonna prompt you for consent.
Right, right, right, right, right, right,
right, right.
I mean, that's, that's the that again,
I think consent is a,
a great example that we could bring up to
the bright SDK team to say, hey,
how are you solving for this?
If you've not we,
we have our own solution, but it's,
it doesn't look like how they would like
it to look like cuz.
This this exact bright assist is what you
guys would currently have in pro.
If you guys have ever used like bright in
pro at the top where it's like how can I
help you right it you could type in
anything anything about pig simply I type
it generate employee statement and I got
some instructions right?
Yep, Yep, Yep.
But that's I haven't implemented any.
Yeah, Yep.
And even though you're like in recruiting,
you could interact with this and ask it
about things outside of that.
That's the whole point of this thing.
But it just means that there's a lot of
things that we would have to do to get it
in there to to make it unified in this
way.
And I guess now I understand better about
when you was saying like a couple of
weeks ago,
like we as the recruiting product need to
have a stance on how we are wanna doing,
we wanna do the bright SDK.
Cuz it's,
it's not just a per agent conversation.
Cuz if you put it here,
it's kind of universal for all recruiting.
It shouldn't just be on one page.
It should be on any of the pages in
recruiting and what it should be able to
do.
So if it's just pools right now and there,
it's probably not super helpful to put it
to put this bright assist MFE everywhere
because the only thing it'll do is tell
you about pools.
It won't tell you about anything else.
So that's another thing.
That's another thing, too.
Like what team is going to move it to be?
I mean, across all recruiting.
That's right.
It's this page.
It's off to me now.
We put it up, although I can't hear you.
You sound really far away.
Yeah, your voice is breaking.
Hello.
You might hear us, but we can't hear you.
Any other questions related to this?
Maybe if you need any other.
If you need PRS that I raised for this
specific task, I can share it with you.
Abhi.
Everything is into rec preview but there
are few things that I did on the bright
hub side.
I'll share that.
If you required the same,
just let me know.
OK?
Sure.
We will let you know.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Nasif,
for going through this.
Josh, are you back?
Since Josh was saying something,
he put his question in the chat.
His question was about what team was
going to be able to move it.
What team is going to be the one to move
it to be for all recruiting pages.
Yeah, it's a great question.
I don't know.
I don't have an answer for you about that
right now.
Yeah, page of recruiting,
I don't know like if the speaker,
but yeah, that was my question.
Like who's gonna,
what team is the one that's gonna move it
for all pages?
Because otherwise if we implement this,
then we're just copying and then putting
it on our page.
But eventually it's gonna have to be
moved for everybody, right?
If we start adding even more,
more like agents to the SDK, right?
Right.
Well, cuz even when I say our page,
our page is like the job board.
It's not really like internal really
anywhere, right?
Ours is the job board.
So we're talking about putting this
brightest MFE on the job board page,
like every job board page.
I think the first step should be like to
move our agents to the respective area to
get it accessible through Bright Assist,
right?
Maybe like we have Eva chat,
Write Job genius and maybe Talent pool
and the interview scorecard, right?
If if we do it for all these four agents
as well,
then we can move it to the global page or
maybe the layout page and like and for
other set of instructions, if any,
if the user input for that,
we can simply add a guardrails in our
agent that I'm specific to do this
particular task.
So we can we can mention that thing and
like like maybe we can,
I can check with Deepti,
but maybe she have some plan in this
context, but I'm not sure about it.
It's all depend on the availability and
as well as the what we are picking up
next depend on that thing as well.
All right, Do we have anything else?
I don't have any more questions.
Yeah,
we missed the stand up Vicki and Josh.
Yeah, I know.
But this this was a good conversation
though this we've we've not had any like
SDK conversation.
So this was very much needed for us.
I agree.
OK, it was much needed.
Yes.
All right, all right.
Anything else if I guess if we have any
questions, we'll we'll be coming to you,
Naseeb.
But for me though,
my take away is the next time that we
have this Bright call with the Bright SDK
team,
that's probably one of the things I'm
gonna bring up is the whole consent
portion of things.
So I appreciate that.
All right.
OK, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Thank you so much, Steve.
Let's sync up.
Vicky and Josh, we can sync up.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Thank you, you guys.
Bye.